jobsnearyou.net 2013-05-25

# Job Search | Search for Jobs Near You. JobsNearYou - Privacy Policy

* Thank you for visiting www.JobsNearYou.net (the “Site,” “JobsNearYou.net), owned and operated by JobsNearYou.net. The Site is an Internet property of JobsNearYou.net and its affiliated companies (“JobsNearYou.net ,” “we” or “us”). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) outlines the privacy practices associated with the Site. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (a) access or use the Site; (b) agree to receive e-mail from us via the Site, or any other means; and/or (c) register on the Site to receive information from third party service providers.

**If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third party for marketing purposes, please e-mail us at info@jobsnearyou.net. Please be advised that where California residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with the law.**

* JobsNearYou.net has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers the website www.JobsNearYou.net. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@myfastonlinesupport.com](mailto:support@myfastonlinesupport.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

* **Personally Identifiable Information Collected**

We collect your personally identifiable information when you sign up to receive job alerts. The types of personally identifiable information that we collect at the Site include, without limitation, your: (a) name; (b) e-mail address; and (c) any and all other information requested on the applicable registration form.

* **Use of Personally Identifiable Information** By submitting your personal information on the Site, you agree that we may send a newsletter to you describing what types of job opportunities in your area. If you wish to opt out of the newsletter, please follow the unsubscribe directions in the email.   
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from user lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. The agents performing these limited functions on our behalf shall have access to our users’ personal information as needed to perform their functions for us but we do not permit them to use your personal information for other purposes.  
We will also use your personal information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request and to customize your experience on the Site. We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our business. We may use third parties to help us operate our business and the Site or to administer activities on our behalf.   
We also reserve the right to release current or past user information in the event that we believe that the user is (i) in violation of the Site’s Terms and Conditions, this Privacy Policy or any other of our operating rules, policies, price schedules and other supplemental terms and conditions or documents that may be published by us from time to time; (ii) to commit unlawful acts; (iii) if such information is subpoenaed or requested pursuant to a judicial or regulatory proceeding or inquiry; (iv) when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others (v) if we are sold or acquired; and/or (vi) when we deem it necessary or appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, and Federal Trade Commission implementing regulations.   
If JobsNearYou.net is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

* We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit many of the pages of the Site. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation, the type of browser that you use, your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider . We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site usage, as well as to offer you products and services. We also reserve the right to use aggregate or group data about our visitors for any and all lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage and/or characteristics of our visitors as a group. By visiting and/or supplying your personal information at the Site, you agree to allow us to provide such aggregate data to third parties.

* **Cookies**

* When an end-user visits the Site, we send a cookie and/or gif file (“Cookie”) to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the applicable end-user’s Internet browser. A Cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience at the Site. To find out more about Cookies, please visit [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/#_blank). To disable and reject certain Cookies, follow the instructions associated with your Internet browser. Even in the case where a user rejects a Cookie, he or she may still use the Promotion Website. JobsNearYou.net reserves the right to retain Cookie data indefinitely.  
The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

* **Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**

* Our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

* **Third Party Links**

* The Website may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites and, where you request information from Third Party Providers, JobsNearYou.net may transfer you directly to the websites of such Third Party Providers. JobsNearYou.net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be required to provide certain information to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and JobsNearYou.net has no responsibility or liability relating to them. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of such website. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. These third party entities are independent third parties and are not affiliated with us.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

* If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete it by making the change on our member information page or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

* **Data Retention**

* We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

* **Social Media Features and Widgets**

* Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

* **Minors**

* We do not knowingly collect information from minors under eighteen (18) years of age. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, the Site by individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

* **Security**

* All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. While we use reasonable, industry standard measures to protect personal information online and offline, no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Access to this personal information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. All of our users’ personal information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personal information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all JobsNearYou.net user personal information. Employees not adhering to our written firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

* **Changes to Privacy Policy**

* We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

* **Contact Us**

* If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at  info@jobsnearyou.net.

JobsNearYou.net   
817 Broadway, Floor 5  
New York NY 10003 

Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we or a data provider we have engaged may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable customized ads or content. No personally identifiable information is placed into these cookies. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.
